<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creations on Edward Leung</title>
    <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creations on Edward Leung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BOSH release for Bamboo &amp; Remote Agents</title>
      <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/examples/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/examples/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>BOSH (Bosh Outer SHell) &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;is an open source tool for release engineering, deployment, lifecycle management, and monitoring of distributed systems.&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s amazingly powerful. This examples uses BOSH to provision an Alassian vendor app running on JDK along with the support Postgres database and agents to support it. The releases manages the health of services and will automatically provision, start/stop processes across the various services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Marketplace Plugins</title>
      <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/examples/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/examples/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coke-Pepsi Classification Model</title>
      <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/cp_classifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/cp_classifier/</guid>
      <description>A deep learning classification model that differenciates between Pepsi and Coke. Using a pre-trained convolution neural network model, ResNet-34, to create a classifier used to determine between Coca-Cola and Pepsi related images taken from Google Images. Manually cleaning and transforming images to create a deeper and richer dataset to improve classification. Trained the classifier with varying learning rates to minimizing errors in the validation set whilst maximizing the accuracy of the model, resulting in an accuracy in the testing set of 97.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker image for Bitbucket CI/CD Pipelines  &#34;shipit&#34;</title>
      <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/examples/docker-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/examples/docker-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Provides required dependencies and additional utilities to simplify and codify the process of building, testing and delivering Atlassian plugins all the way to the live marketplace.Executes integration/AUT level tests against all stated compatible versions for the productUploads generated artifact to Atlassian marketplaceProvides corresponding metadata indicating version, release notes, and compatibility</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Quantum Challenge</title>
      <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/quantum_challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/quantum_challenge/</guid>
      <description>Manipulating Qubits into Bell and GHZ states and interpreting its results on a real noisy quantum computer. A simulation of the BB84 protocol, an application of a Quantum computer to encrypt and decrypt messages between two parties. Approximated a unitary using only U3 and CX gates with a focus on cost and accuracy resulting in a total cost of 310. Solution of unitary resulted in 375th place out of the total 1745 participants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion Activated Soap Dispenser</title>
      <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/soap_dispenser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/soap_dispenser/</guid>
      <description>Developed a C program using MCUXpresso for the LPC804 microcontroller, utilizing internal clocks and system interrupts to communicate with a 7-segment display, servo motor, ultrasonic sensor, and push button. Communication between microcontroller and peripherals use protocols such as GPIO, PWM and internal timers such as System Tick, Multi-rate, and Self-Wake-up. Designed and created for an embedded systems course, received a final grade of A+.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titanic Survival Predictor</title>
      <link>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/titanic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>xoreus.github.io/projects/creations/titanic/</guid>
      <description>Applying factors such as age, sex, and fare type of passengers who had survived the disaster to train a logistic regression model using the scikit-learn library. Using the trained model to predict if a passenger would survive based on the same factors; scored a 77.5% accuracy rating based on Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s scoring system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>